God is still saying something.
During a live service at The SCOAN,
Prophet T.B Joshua gave a prophecy concerning Abuja, the capital of Nigeria.
These were his words:
Listen to me, my people in Nigeria.
Once again, take note of this:
Our security should be vigilant.
I am seeing a very big strike - explosion.
They should take care of Abuja - capital.
When I talk, you see me in a bad light, but I will keep talking.
I don't need to say the state, but I am saying it.
This is what I am seeing happen in Abuja.
They should pray!
What can they do to capture this?
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations,
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 25/03/2019